http://www.voiceofcare.org/privacy-notice.html

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy covers Voice of Care’s treatment of personal information or personally identifiable information that may be collected or submitted when the web-user is using Voice of Care’s website or services. This policy does not apply to companies that Voice of Care does not own or control, or to individuals that are not under Voice of Care’s supervisory control. Please understand that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online this information cannot be made one-hundred percent secure and, in some cases, that information can be intercepted, collected and used by others. However, we work hard to protect your information at all times, and protect your information in several ways. Your information is stored on a secure server that Voice of Care and its authorized personnel can only access through a password.It is our Voice of Care policy that your information will never be intentionally shared with a third party without your knowledge and permission.Voice of Care may use the personal information you provide for purposes such as: carrying out a registration made by you or fulfilling your requests for information, products, or services; Voice of Care may also retain the details of registrations and may issue invitations to other Voice of Care programming or events. Voice of Care may use your information to apprise you of organization news or support opportunities. Information on purchases and other transactions or payments through our secure third party payment server, First Data, may be retain in their secure system.This website contains links to other third party websites, primarily for providing resource connections. Voice of Care is not responsible for how other organizations handle any information solicited via their websites.If you have questions, or believe that private information has been mistakenly shared with Voice of Care, please contact office@voiceofcare.org with your concerns.
Voice of Care is a Recognized Service Organization of the Lutheran Church Missouri Synod. © Voice of Care 2018 all rights reserved.   Privacy Notice     Contact Us
Site powered by Weebly. Managed by Lunarpages
Home
About
Guiding Statements
Strategic Plan
The Voice of Care Story
Voice of Care Values
Voice of Care Team
